alright guys welcome back to another video and this is definitely going to be
好吧欢迎回到 另一个人 视频，这肯定 会是
the coolest tutorial yet because I'm going to be showing you guys how to make
最酷的教程，因为我 要 展示你们 如何 使
a web crawler some people may call them spiders but they're basically programs
一个人可能会打电话给 他们的网络爬虫 蜘蛛，但他们基本上是程序
that you can give it any URL you want and they can go to that web page and
你可以给它任何你想要的URL 他们可以 去该 网页和
they can either it can actually do a couple things you can either just gather
他们可以实际做到 你 可以聚在一起的几件事
information from that web page or it could find all the links and go on to
来自该网页的信息 可以找到所有链接并继续
those web pages pretty much crawl the web the most popular web crawler is
那些 网页几乎爬行了 web是最受欢迎的网络爬虫
probably Google's which goes through a bunch of pages gathers information for a search engine so of course we're not
也许谷歌的 哪些经历 一个 一堆网页 收集 信息的 搜索引擎， 所以当然我们不是
going to be building one that big but this one is actually going to be pretty
将建立 一个 大而重要的 这个实际上会很漂亮
cool and also the reason I had this page up is because I'm not sure what websites
很酷，也是我 有这个页面 的原因 起来是因为我 不确定是什么网站
actually allow you to curl them I'm pretty sure like um eBay or Craigslist
实际上让你卷曲他们我 非常肯定像你的eBay或Craigslist
it's against their Terms of Service like I don't know that for sure but I'm like
这是对他们的服务条款的 像 我不确定， 但我喜欢
they probably don't want you doing it so I figured just to test this out just so I wouldn't get in trouble I'm just doing
他们可能不希望你这样做使 我想这只是为了测试它 我不会遇到麻烦 ，我只是在做
it on one of my own web pages so if you go to Bucky's room org slash trade slash
它在我 自己的一个网页上， 所以如果你 去Bucky的房间org斜线贸易斜线
index dot PHP this is a section on my website where I let users like trade
index dot PHP 这 是我的一个部分 网站 ， 我让用户喜欢交易
items so this is the home page right here and it's actually kind of important
项目所以这是主页权利 在这里 ， 它实际上 很重要
to see the structure of it now if you go to search this is the page that we're going to be curling so of course this
如果 你去 ，现在看看它的结构 搜索这 是 我们 的页面 当然要卷曲吧
lists all the items in all the categories and if you notice a couple things we want to take note of it has a
列出所有的所有项目 类别，如果你注意到一对 我们 要注意的 事情有一个
couple pages that the items are on so then only less 30 items per page and
几 页 的项目 上，从而 然后每页只有不到30个项目 和
we're going to be using this parameter right here the page number and we're
我们将 使用此参数 就在这里页码，我们是
going to be giving our spider that information so it isn't just stuck on
将给我们的蜘蛛 信息所以它不仅仅是坚持下去
one page the whole time so what our web crawler is going to do is go page by
一页一页所以我们的网站 爬虫要做的就是去页面
page and it can either just gather the links or maybe you can just gather the
页面 ，它可以只收集 链接或者你可以收集
titles whatever we want it to do but anyways that is how my website is laid out so let's go ahead and open pycharm
标题无论我们想要它做什么，但是 无论如何，这 是我的 网站奠定了 出来 让我们继续打开 pycharm
and start coding this bad boy now there are couple modules that we
并开始 编码这个坏男孩 现在有几个模块，我们
need to import first the first is requests and that's because remember this is whenever you're connecting to
需要先导入第一个是 请求，那是因为记住 这是你连接的时候
the Internet in Python this is well it's my favorite way to there's actually a
Python中 的互联网 就是这样 我最喜欢的方式实际上是
couple different ways but this is to request information from a web page and another thing that we're going to need
夫妻不同的方式， 但这是 请求来自网页的信息和 另一件我们需要的东西
is my favorite module of all time so go to settings and this is when I was
是我最喜欢的模块， 所以去吧 设置，这是我的时间
changing the font size for the video all right where am I get out of that so go
更改视频的字体大小 我离开 的地方就这样走了
to project interpreter and that's where you can see all your modules and the package or module that we want to import
项目翻译，那是在哪里 你可以看到你所有的模块和 我们要导入的包或模块
is called beautiful soup 4 so again if you don't have this added which you
如果，再称为美丽的汤 4 你没有这个 添加你
probably don't just add it like before I showed you in the I don't know like
可能不只是像我之前那样添加它 告诉你我不 知道喜欢
couple tutorials ago look for a beautiful soup for and what this is is
几个教程前 寻找一个 美丽的汤 ，这是什么
it's your module that lets you pretty much go to a website and in sort through
这是你的模块让 你漂亮 很多去网站和排序
data so right now that request is kind of limited because it can connect to a
数据所以现在 请求 是善意的 限制 因为它可以连接 到
webpage but it's kind of dumb so what beautiful soup for allows you to do is
网页， 但它有点愚蠢，所以 美丽的汤 让你做的就是
pretty much look at all the page source and you can say things like ok get all
几乎看看 所有页面源 你可以说 好的 事情可以 得到所有
the links from this page or get all the you know headers or titles or anything
来自此页面的链接或获取所有 你知道标题或标题或任何东西
like that so you guys are going to be seeing how cool it is later on but anyways whenever you have it installed
像这样你们 将要 看看以后有多酷，但是 无论何时安装它，无论如何
what you can say is from bs4 import beautiful soup and that's going to
你能说的是来自bs4 import 美丽的汤，这将是
import all the tools that we need and again if you're ever looking at
导入所有我们需要的工具 和 再次，如果你一直在看
documentation to use this online it's either you can type in beautiful soup
这是在线使用它的文档 要么你可以输入美味的汤
bs4 arm beautiful suit for and the web page is going to pop up so you know if
bs4 arm美丽的西装和网络 页面将弹出， 所以你知道是否
you ever want more information than just giving you guys a heads up so now we
你想要更多的信息而不仅仅是 现在我们 给 你们一个抬头
imported all the crap we need and the first thing I actually want to do is
导入我们需要的所有垃圾 和 我真正想做的第一件事就是
go back to your main search so by default
回到你的主搜索所以 默认
we're just on this page right now and this is the page that we're going to
我们只是这个网页上 ，现在 和 这是我们要的页面
start from the main search page so make sure you're on this right here not on
从主搜索页面开始， 以便制作 确定你就在这里，而不是在这里
any not like on page three or anything like that so the first thing I want to do is I wanted to make the core spider
任何不喜欢第三页或任何东西 像那样， 我想要的第一件事 做的是我想做的核心蜘蛛
just the main spider that can sift through and we'll just do something
只是 可以 筛选 的主要蜘蛛 通过 ，我们会做点什么
really simple at first before we get to advanced so since this is a spider
在 我们到达 之前 ， 一开始 真的很 简单 由于这是一只蜘蛛，所以先进了
that's going to be limited to the trading section on my website I just
这将限于 在我的网站交易区 我只是
want to name it trade spider so after this what I want to do is I actually want to give it a parameter of
想把它命名为交易 蜘蛛 所以在此之后我想做的就是我 其实想给它的参数
max pages because whenever we're testing things out say we're just testing it for
最大 页面，因为每当我们测试 东西出来说我们 只是测试它
the first time make sure it can gather links or something well I don't want it
第一次确保它可以聚集 链接或东西我不想要它
to crawl all these pages what if there's a hundred pages well if something isn't
抓取所有这些页面，如果有的话 如果不是，那就好一百页
working in our program it's going to take a while to you know go through and
我们的计划正在进行中 花一点时间，你知道经历和
find the bug so whenever I have this parameter max pages by default we can
每当我有这个时，就找到这个bug 我们可以默认参数max pages
just set it equal to one or two at first and then once everything's working we'll just set equal to like 50 or however
只是将其设置 为一个 或两个 在第一 然后一旦一切正常，我们就会 只是设置为等于喜欢 50 或然而
many pages we want to curl so by default I'm going to set page equal to one so
默认情况下 我们 想要 卷曲的很多页面 我要将页面设置为等于1
this is going to change every time it loop through a page so basically it's going to do this crawl this page and
这种情况 每次都会发生变化 循环浏览页面所以基本上就是这样 要做这个抓取这个页面 和
then in our spider we're going to set that variable equal to page two and that
然后在我们的蜘蛛中我们要设置 该变量 等于第二页和那个
way it knows to go to page two right there because of course this is a
它知道如何去第二页吧 因为当然这是 一个
program it can't actually like click buttons on your web page so that's why
程序它实际上不 喜欢点击 您的网页上的按钮， 这就是原因
we need to throw in everything in parameters so once we have that what we
我们需要的一切扔在 参数，所以一旦我们拥有了我们
need to do is we need to make a wild loop so we're going to say while the
需要做的是我们需要做一个狂野的 循环所以我们要 同时说
page number is less than max pages so again we're going to go through the
页码小于最大页数 我们又要经历了
pages one by one and it's going to stop whenever we get to max pages so if we
页面一个接一个 ，它会停止 每当我们达到 最大页面时，如果我们
pass in 10 right here it's going to say okay
在这里传递10，它会 说 好的
I'm pretty much going to crawl 10 pages simple enough so the first thing I want to do is actually the first thing that
我几乎要爬 10页 这么 简单， 所以我想要的第一件事 这样做实际上是 第一 件事 ，
we need to do is we need to build the basic URL because it's saying okay I am
我们需要做的是我们 需要 建立 基本的URL， 因为它说 我 没事
a web crawler but you kind of need to give me a web page of the curl
一个网络爬虫，但你需要 给我卷曲的网页
well the web page is this if you copy that URL again around page 2 but we'll
如果你复制，网页就是这个 该网址再次 围绕第2页，但我们会
fix that right now again of course the easier thing to do is just throw all of
当然再解决这个问题 更简单的事情就是扔掉 所有的东西
this in a variable so I'm going to name it URL and this is the URL that it's
这是一个变量所以我要命名 它是URL，这是它的 URL
going to curl so set this equal to this right here now if we just left this as
要卷曲所以设置它等于这个 就在这里， 如果我们刚离开这个
is then every single time it would just crow page number two and that's
那么每一次它都会 乌鸦第二页， 那是
obviously not what we want so what we want to do is actually delete this last
显然不是 我们想要的， 所以我们 想要做的其实就是删除这个
number right here and the page that we want it to crow is whatever page this
数字就在这里和我们的页面 想要 乌鸦是这个什么页面
variable is equal to so get this base URL and then on the end of it
变量等于得到这个基数 URL然后在它的末尾
Tech on STR page so again if this variable changes every time the URL the
STR页面上的技术， 如果这样的话 每次URL都变量变化
first time is going to be page 1 then page 2 and page 3 and it's going to go
第一次将是第1页 ，然后 第2页和第3页， 它将会 去
all the way until it gets the however many pages we told it to curl so that's
一直到它 得到了 很多页面我们告诉它卷曲这样的
how you can have your URL change every single time so now we have a URL what do
如何让你的 网址每次更改 单次所以现在我们有 一个 URL做什么
we need to do now well what we need to do is actually request the data from
我们现在需要做好我们需要的工作 do实际上是从中请求数据
that website or connect to that website through Python so the results that we
该网站或连接 到该网站 通过Python所以我们的结果
get back I'm going to be storing in a variable called source code and set this
我会回来的 变量称为源代码并设置此项
equal to request dot get URL so again each time this loops it's going to
等于 所以再次请求点获取网址 每次这个循环就会发生
connect to that web page and store the results in a variable car called source
连接到该网页并 存储 导致变量汽车称为源
code so basically what we have now is as you Alvie page source it'll be easier
码 所以我们现在基本上就像你一样 Alvie页面源它会更容易
basically what we have now is all of this crap stored in that variable
基本上我们现在已经是所有的 这个垃圾存储在那个变量中
however whenever you connect to a website it's a little bit more complex
但是每当你连接到一个 网站有点复杂
than just getting the page source it also comes with other stuff like headers
而不只是 获取页面源它 还附带其他东西，如标题
I don't know I don't even know if you guys know what headers are but they're
我不知道我甚至都不 知道 你 伙计们知道标题是什么，但他们是
the extra stuff that like your um well it's like extra crap that the user
像 你 这样的额外的东西 它就像是用户的额外垃圾
doesn't need to know about it's probably the easiest example but all we really
并不需要 了解它可能 最简单的 例子，但我们真的
want is that um source code so what I can do now is I can put plain underscore
想要的是那个源 代码所以我 现在可以做的是我可以用 简单的下划线
text or you can name your variable anything you want and if you put
文本或您可以命名您的变量 你想要什么，如果你放